[
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "02A_Side01_ReapersLocus",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 35,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "02A_Side01_ReapersLocus_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0210a_Barkeep",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "02_Quest_Obelisk_11",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99B_MSQ_12 || 99_MSQ_34",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "02A_Side01_ReapersLocus_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Reaper's Locus (Expedition)",
        "Description": "Defeat the Starstone Reaper and Collect the Reaper's Locus. Talk to Herbalist Lau in the Brightwood Settlement when the task is done.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Really? Why?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Because I plan on staying here! And that means I should make this town a better place.\\n\\nBut unlike you, I'm no warrior.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Before you go marching into the Shattered Obelisk, I'd suggest finding some friends.\\n\\nThe Reaper isn't the only horror prowling those ruins.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Oh, it's about time. You're such a talent, I frankly expected you to return much sooner.\\n\\nBut don't get me wrong--I'm very grateful. I'll take the Locus, and you can have this.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "02A_Side02_01_Secrets",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "02A_Side02_01_Secrets_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0203a_Survivalist_1a",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "02_Quest_04",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99B_MSQ_06 || 99_MSQ_34",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "02A_Side02_01_Secrets_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "Secrets of the Earth",
        "Description": "Collect spores from Bronzeroot Warriors in Pendle Hollow and bone dust from the Lost at Pendleton. Return to Embalmer Bankole when the task is complete.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"We should feel sorry for the Lost?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Of course.\\n\\nI have been here longer than these others, long enough that no one listens to old Bankole any more.",
        "InProgressResponse": "The Bronzeroot Warriors are a new expression of the Angry Earth, but they know the old ways.\\n\\nI only hope my efforts do not add to the suffering of the Lost.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "These satchels... their scent... do you smell it?  Moss spores.\\n\\nIt makes sense, does it not? That which withers with half-death is susceptible to the energy of fresh life.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "02A_Side02_02_EarthProvide",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "02A_Side02_02_EarthProvide_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0203a_Survivalist_2",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "02_Quest_05",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "02_Quest_04",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "02A_Side02_02_EarthProvide_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "Earth Will Provide",
        "Description": "Defeat the Bronzewood Dryads who are guarding stores of precious alkahest. Meet back up with Embalmer Bankole east of Bronzegrove.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Don't know where I'd find that.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Fortunately, I do.\\n\\nThe Angry Earth have overrun Ancient ruins to the south. There may still be rare reagents in the ruins, though you will have to cut a path through the dryads.",
        "InProgressResponse": "What drew the Angry Earth into the ruins?\\n\\nDid they seek power within? We may never knowâ€¦",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "A potent alkahest? Perfect, perfect.\\n\\nI did not think anyone else would consider the plight of the Lost. But you have. Thank you.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "02A_Side03_01_Infernal",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "02A_Side03_01_Infernal_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0230a_Ranger_2",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "02_Quest_16",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99B_MSQ_02 || 99_MSQ_34",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "02A_Side03_01_Infernal_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "Infernal Armaments",
        "Description": "Disrupt the Corrupted war effort by defeating their leaders at Corlew's Mine and Shervey's Lumbermill. Then meet with Ranger Shui Tijong outside of Calvary.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"That seems to work.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "The main thrust of the Corrupted operations here is the mission to supply their forces with armaments.\\n\\nThey have a start-to-finish process under way, mining the ore and forging the weapons.",
        "InProgressResponse": "We cannot let them keep extracting resources from the land.\\n\\nThere is barely enough to sustain the people of Brightwood as it is.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Well done. They still control both locations, but it won't do them much good.\\n\\nBut you look troubled. Did you discover something?",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "02A_Side03_02_Belly",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "02A_Side03_02_Belly_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0230a_Ranger_3",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "02_Quest_17",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "02_Quest_16",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "02A_Side03_02_Belly_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "Belly of the Corrupted",
        "Description": "Sabotage the food supply chain for the Corrupted at Reida's Burrow. Talk to Ranger Shui Tijong near Calvary when the task is done.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"We should strike there next.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "My thoughts exactly - we can warn the settlement later.  We must strike hard and fast.\\n\\nI have been watching the Corrupted forces' movements since they arrived.",
        "InProgressResponse": "If we destroy the hunters and claim all their rations, the Corrupted forces' supply lines will be in dire straits.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Well done, friend. With their rations stolen and their hunters compromised, the Corrupted will be hungry.\\n\\nHungry soldiers are desperate soldiers and desperate soldiers are sloppy.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "02A_Side04_01_Location",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 26,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "02A_Side04_01_Location_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0231a_Painter",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "02_Quest_19",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99B_MSQ_05 || 99_MSQ_34",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "02A_Side04_01_Location_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "Location Scout",
        "Description": "Search for vibrant waterfalls for Wolcott to paint and place an easel at each one. Talk to Painter Wolcott in Brightwood when the task is done.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"You donâ€™t have time?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Sadly, I donâ€™t have time to both find all the beautiful locations and paint them. Searching cannot be rushed, and it takes me so long to get my paints arranged just how I like them.\\n\\nBut perhaps you could help!",
        "InProgressResponse": "I need some inspiration, something that jumps out of the landscape and onto a canvas!\\n\\nGo on, I'm counting on you to find it!",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Marvelous! The rushing water, the way the sunlight glints through the trees. Yes, yes! I can work with this.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "Brightwoodv2Arc4",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "02A_Side04_02_Reflection",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 27,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "02A_Side04_02_Reflection_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0231a_Painter",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "02_Quest_20",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "02_Quest_19",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "02A_Side04_02_Reflection_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "Eye for Reflection",
        "Description": "Search for dynamic waterfalls for Wolcott to paint and place an easel at each one. Talk to Painter Wolcott in Brightwood when the task is done.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"The power?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "How dynamic it makes an image. How alive you feel when seeing it. How it moves, even when still.\\n\\nI can already tell these waterfalls will be best sellers. Iâ€™m going to need more locations!",
        "InProgressResponse": "You were such help before that I need your help again.\\n\\nSearch for energetic waterfalls I can use as reference.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "These are magnificent! Thank you for marking their locations on my map. I can only hope my waterfall paintings are able to compete with what is already out there.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "Brightwoodv2Arc4",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "02A_Side04_03_Masterpiece",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 28,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "02A_Side04_03_Masterpiece_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0231a_Painter",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "02_Quest_21",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "02_Quest_20",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "02A_Side04_03_Masterpiece_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "Wolcott's Masterpiece",
        "Description": "Search for picturesque lakes for Wolcott to paint and place an easel at each one. Talk to Painter Wolcott in Brightwood when the task is done.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"There are some nice lakes around here.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Iâ€™ve decided that my next collection of paintings will be of the local lakes.\\n\\nSomething restful to the eye, and calming to the soul. They are certain to be popular!",
        "InProgressResponse": "The waterfalls you found before were just lovely.\\n\\nNow I need three lakes for my next paintings!",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Superb! The locations you have chosen fit perfectly within the landscape, like a slice of sky fallen to the ground.\\n\\nPainting these lakes will be a joy. And Cole hasnâ€™t painted anything like them yet!",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "Brightwoodv2Arc4",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "02A_Side05_01_Tea",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "02A_Side05_01_Tea_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0232a_Naturalist_2",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "02_Quest_22",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99B_MSQ_06 || 99_MSQ_34",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "02A_Side05_01_Tea_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "A Simple Tea",
        "Description": "Collect Undefiled Tea Leaves from Verdant Cavern and Lush Sugarsap from the Lush Hideaway. Bring them back to Naturalist Khunbish in Brightwood.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"What do you need?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "The soullessness of the Lost has ravaged Brightwood for centuries. Some say the land is cursed.\\n\\nBut the Angry Earth thrive down there, despite all the death around them.",
        "InProgressResponse": "I do not only ask for tea ingredients for myself.\\n\\nCollect the leaves and honey, and I will share my recipe with you.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Ah, do you have them, then? Yes, these leaves are perfect!\\n\\nThe tea I can brew from these leaves, well, I am not even sure of all of its properties.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "02A_Side05_02_Achene",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "02A_Side05_02_Achene_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0232a_Naturalist_3",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "02_Quest_25",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "02_Quest_22",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "02A_Side05_02_Achene_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "Azoth Tree Achene",
        "Description": "Defeat the Angry Earth Leader Ceran at the Azoth Tree and collect his Achene. Talk to Naturalist Khunbish in Brightwood when the task is done.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"What? I didn't agree to anything else.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "No? Do you not wish to slash, burn, and loot? Is that not what your kind does?\\n\\nNo matter. You must defeat a dryad named Ceran.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Ceranâ€¦ how long has it been?\\n\\nHe hoped I had forgotten. But I do not forget, and I do not forgive.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Ceran is gone, and you have restored the true order here.\\n\\nIf you wish it, you have earned the whole truth.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "02A_Side06_01_Bears",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "02A_Side06_01_Bears_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0233a_Hunter",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "02_Quest_26",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99B_MSQ_05 || 99_MSQ_34",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "02A_Side06_01_Bears_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "Bear Co-Habitation",
        "Description": "Help Hunter Hutchison in Brightwood get vengeance against some savage bears in Greyvale that destroyed his family.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"You don't live there any more?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "No. They don't want me. They've made that painfully clear.\\n\\nMy wife Susan and I lived among them for decades, in perfect harmony. Until a few months ago.",
        "InProgressResponse": "I still can't get over it. Out of nowhere, they just turned on us.\\n\\nHelp me get my vengeance, and I'll be in your debt.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "I heard those bastards snarling and growling all the way down here.\\n\\nWhy, we're only giving them what they deserve.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "02A_Side06_02_PapaBear",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "02A_Side06_02_PapaBear_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0233a_Hunter",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "02_Quest_27",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "02_Quest_26",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "02A_Side06_02_PapaBear_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "Papa Bear (Elite)",
        "Description": "Hunter Hutchison has asked you to destroy Gren, the massive bear who killed his wife, and reclaim his wife's ring. Bring the ring back to Hunter Hutchinson in Brightwood.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Any family anywhere?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Nah, Susan and these bears are the only real family I ever had.\\n\\nLiving out there, foraging for honey, hibernatingâ€¦ it's the only life I know, the only place I feel at home.",
        "InProgressResponse": "It was that monster Gren that ate my sweet wife.\\n\\nDestroy him, and then I can return to the family, those I have left.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "It's done then? That monstrosity of a bear gone? You're a brave soul, and a hardy one too.\\n\\nAll right, I'll work up the nerve and go back home. If they turn on me again, I don't know. Guess I'll end up like Susan.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "02A_Side07_01_Memories",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "02A_Side07_01_Memories_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0234a_Mourner_2",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "02_Quest_28",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_20",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "02A_Side07_01_Memories_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "Memories of Another Life",
        "Description": "Megara Pantazis lived in the Walsham area many decades ago. She's asked you to retrieve her mementos from the town and return them to her in Brightwood so she can relive her past.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"What happened?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "The town of Walsham fell to the Lostâ€¦ it's been more years than I can count.\\n\\nBelieve it or not, the wedding was on this very spot--a moment I never want to forget. He was the love of my life.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Those years in Walsham were the best I had.\\n\\nIf you could recover those mementos, it would mean a lot.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "I'm amazed. You managed to find all these pieces of my past, even my old diary.\\n\\nIt's sad, isnâ€™t it? Or it should be.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "02A_Side07_02_Death",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 28,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "02A_Side07_02_Death_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0234a_Mourner_2",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "02_Quest_30",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "02_Quest_28",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "02A_Side07_02_Death_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "Til Death do us Part",
        "Description": "Megara Pantazis has admitted the love of her life was actually Pastor Prewitt. She's asked you be sure nothing of his human nature remains. Talk to her in Brightwood when the task is complete.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"When what truth came out?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "The truth about my true love. I didn't tell you the whole story.\\n\\nThe wedding that took place here, it wasn't where I married my true love, it's where I met him.",
        "InProgressResponse": "My love was a formidable man in life.\\n\\nI suspect he will be difficult to defeat. Do take care.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Tell me, did you see him? Did he seem miserable as a Lost, or actually at peace? What did you find?\\n\\nWhat is this?",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "02A_Side08_01_Treasures",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "02A_Side08_01_Treasures_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0249a_Aethelwynn_2",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "02A_SQ_01",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99B_MSQ_01 || 99_MSQ_34",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "02A_Side08_01_Treasures_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "Earthly Treasures",
        "Description": "Aethelwynn, a self-proclaimed treasure hunter, needs help finding lucrative graves in Brightwood. Find records of Brightwood's residents, then return to Aethelwynn near Deggendorf.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"This isn't a very friendly place.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "You don't need to tell me twice. The Lost get violent when you poke through their houses.\\n\\nOh, don't look at me like that. Everyone has to make a living.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Do you think the Lost remember anything they did when they were alive?\\n\\nHmmâ€¦no, forget it. Just thinking about it gives me the shivers.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Just about done reading through these records.\\n\\nMy eyes are swimming, but it'll be worth it in the end. It has to be.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "Brightwoodv2Arc3",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "02A_Side08_02_LostReturned",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "02A_Side08_02_LostReturned_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0249a_Aethelwynn_2a",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "02A_SQ_02",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "02A_SQ_01",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "02A_Side08_02_LostReturned_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "Lost and Returned",
        "Description": "Aethelwynn has identified two promising graves that might contain treasure. Scatter the lost defending the coffins, and investigate each grave. Then, return to Aethelwynn with your spoils.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"So now we find treasures?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Yes! Maybe. I hope so.\\n\\nSome coffins in Brightwood weren'tâ€¦ buried properly, if you catch my meaning. Let's start with the easy pickings and see what we find.",
        "InProgressResponse": "The coffins should be pretty old by now, so a good push will force their lids off.\\n\\nDon't ask me how I know.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Is that a basket? Ohâ€¦ the color's still as bright as a robin's egg.\\n\\nFair's fair, and I promised to split the treasure with you. You keep the coin, and I'll take this basket.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "Brightwoodv2Arc3",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "02A_Side08_03_Music",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "02A_Side08_03_Music_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0249a_Aethelwynn_3",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "02A_SQ_03",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "02A_SQ_02",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "02A_Side08_03_Music_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "Music to Her Ears",
        "Description": "Though nervous about its fearful reputation, Aethelwynn still wants to see if there's treasure in the old Cathedral and its neighboring village. Investigate each location, then return to Aethelwynn.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"You sound nervous.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Nervous? Me? I suppose it's pretty obvious.\\n\\nThe next spot for buried treasure is the old cathedral north of the town. But I've heard terrible tales about it for years. Howling Lost, shadows that strangle intruders...",
        "InProgressResponse": "I heard that a fire-spewing demon lives under the floorboards of the cathedral.\\n\\nIt's probably not true. Right? Right, definitely not true.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "What an adorable flute! May I?\\n\\nI'll bet it plays the sweetest songs. Can I keep this, for my share? And the whittling knife, in case I want to add any carvings to it.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "Brightwoodv2Arc3",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "02A_Side08_04_Legacy",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "02A_Side08_04_Legacy_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0249a_Aethelwynn_5",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "02A_SQ_04",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "02A_SQ_03",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "02A_Side08_04_Legacy_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "Dark Legacy",
        "Description": "Though Aethelwynn said she would meet you later, she is nowhere to be seen. Mortemer's Manor and Brightrest Cemetery seem to be the most likely locations to find her.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Hi, there. Good boy.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "(The dog perks up and sniffs your clothes.\\n\\nHe swings his snout around, pointing toward the cluster of houses around Mortimer's Manor.)",
        "InProgressResponse": "(The dog looks at you with plaintive eyes.\\n\\nIt seems like he wants to come with you to Mortimer's Manor, but fears the Lost.)",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "O-oh. It's y-you. S-sorry I didn't meet you like I said I would.\\n\\nI promise I didn't forget, I've just beenâ€¦ it's not important. Anyway, did you find anything good in the cemetery?",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "Brightwoodv2Arc3",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "02A_Side08_05_Reunion",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "02A_Side08_05_Reunion_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0249a_Aethelwynn_6",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "02A_SQ_05",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "02A_SQ_04",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "02A_Side08_05_Reunion_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "Reunion",
        "Description": "Aethelwynn is finally ready to face her past and tell you what she's been seeking. Help her track down her brother-in-law by searching nearby villages, then return to her at the spirit shrine.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"I just want to know the truth.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "It's no different from any other sorry tale of Brightwood. My mother succumbed to despair first and then the Vigil put my father \"under guard.\"\\n\\nBy the endâ€¦ they were ready to bury all of us alive.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Roderick used to fight for the Bright Vigil. I never heard what happened to him.\\n\\nI hopeâ€¦ no, maybe it's best not to hope at this point.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "That's Roderick's shield. But you found no other trace of him?\\n\\nThen at least I can hope that he left the Vigil behind, and found a better life elsewhere.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "Brightwoodv2Arc3",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "02A_Side08_06_Heart",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "02A_Side08_06_Heart_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0249a_Aethelwynn_6",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "02A_SQ_06",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "02A_SQ_05",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "02A_Side08_06_Heart_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "Heart of Darkness (Elite)",
        "Description": "Aethelwynn suspects that her sister's necklace is in the greedy hands of Archminister Havelock. Destroy him, find the necklace, and return to Aethelwynn at the spirit shrine.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"I'll get it back. You need closure.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "And a bit of revenge. If Havelock suffers for what he did to my family, so much the better.\\n\\nHe'll be holed up on the island. The Vigil kept their treasury there.",
        "InProgressResponse": "I thought I'd feel better by now, but I'm just nervous. And more than a little scared for you.\\n\\nPlease be careful. You're a good person, and I don't want to see you hurt.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "You really did it. Emmeline's necklace. See the little charm at the end?\\n\\nAt first, I regretted coming back. So many old ghosts. But I can start putting them to rest, thanks to you.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    }
]
